pirateunblocker.com 2011-10-30

# Privacy policy

#### Privacy policy

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use this site. 

##### Log files

We reserve the right to monitor and log your access to this service including your Internet Protocol address, the browser you used to visit our site , the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site and other websites accessed using this service. 

##### Cookies and web beacons

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

These third-party advertisers may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on this website. The following are the advertisers:

Please see the complete [list of 3rd party advertisers](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=94149).

To prevent cookies being placed on your computer by these advertisers please visit their websites and opt out of cookies if such an option is available. You can also opt-out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the [network advertiser's opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). You can also disable cookies in your web browser's options. Consult your web browser's documentation for more information.

#####  Google and the doubleclick DART 

The third party vendors google and doubleclick use a cookie called DART to track your visits to various websites on the Internet. This data is used to serve you ads based on your interests. You may opt out of this cookie by visiting [google's privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You may also find more information about the DART cookie on [doubleclick's privacy policy FAQ](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)

© 2008 this site
